

# KELVIN LEUNG

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

# **ABOUT ME**

A positive and self-motivated full-stack developer with 7+ years of work experience in many different front-end and back-end languages, responsive frameworks, database, mobile app development with Java for Android devices & Swift for iOS devices, and best code practices.

#### CONTACT

#### Address:

Brisbane, Australia

### Email:

kelvinleung.aus@gmail.com

#### Website:

http://kelvinleung.me

# LinkedIn:

https://linkedin.com/in/kelvinlwy

#### GitHub:

https://github.com/kelvinlwy

# **SKILLS**

# **Mobile Development:**

Android • iOS

# **Programming Languages:**

JS • Java • Swift • Objective-C • PHP • SQL

#### Web Technologies:

Node.js • CSS3 • HTML5 • Jquery • ReactJs • React Native • AngularJs

# Database:

MySQL • PostgreSQL • MongoDB

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Co-Founder & Tech Lead

2017 - Present

#### **HAPPY DINOSAUR PTY LTD**

Happy Dinosaur is an advertising startup which has established an innovative strategy to utilise takeaway coffee cup as medium and cafes as hubs for delivering business messages to target local audiences.

My lead role is to design & develop both web & mobile platform for online system through performing requirements analysis, design, technology sourcing to implementation, maintenance, and product analysis; manage digital marketing and social media advertising.

# Full Stack Web App Developer

Mar, 2017 - Sep, 2017

#### **CHAPTECH**

I am responsible for building a web platform written in modern software technologies. My responsibilities:

- Develop a complex web application from scratch for both frontend (with HTML5, CSS3, ReactJS) and backend (with Hapi.js, Node.js, MySQL)
- Implement GIS by using Mapbox API
- API design and development
- Testing, debugging, troubleshooting, maintainence, and application stability & performance improvement

# Android Lead & Web Developer

May 2016 - Mar, 2017

#### **IRECRUIT AUSTRALIA**

I am responsible for the full lifecycle Android development through design, project architecture, implementation to debugging & troubleshooting, testing, and product release; the web application front-end development from project planning to translating UI design into code and handling & presenting business logic visually in the web interface.

# **Mobile App Developer**

Jun 2011 - Apr, 2016

#### LOCATRIX COMMUNICATIONS

- Professional Android development with Java & iOS development with Swift
- Involved in full lifecycle mobile app development for both enterprise internal & commerical products from the ground up to ready-to-go product

# Customer Service Coordinator

**VANTEC WORLD TRANSPORT(HK) LTD** 

**Air Export Ops Officer** 

**UPS SUPPLY CHAIN SOLUTIONS** 

# **EDUCATION**

# **Griffith University**

# **BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING**

2008 - 2011

Bachelor of Engineering, Electronic & Computer Engineering with Class IIA Honours

# **REFERENCE**

# ALEKSANDAR SVETSKI

Former CEO, iRecruit Australia Phone: +61 417 165 003

# MARK WHITE

CEO, Locatrix Communications
Phone: +61 438 900 880